<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ftard.me</title>
    <link>http://ftard.me/</link>
    <description>Recent content on ftard.me</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2020 13:37:25 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://ftard.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Testing</title>
      <link>http://ftard.me/posts/testing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 19:17:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ftard.me/posts/testing/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brix Kvm Server</title>
      <link>http://ftard.me/posts/content/brix-kvm-server/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 06:30:57 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ftard.me/posts/content/brix-kvm-server/</guid>
      <description>With Ubuntu Server LTS 20.04 Getting my realtek nic to work
When I was deleting Debian Buster on my brix machine, I tried to save as many notes and config files for future reference. Anything that would help me remember how to set up KVM from scratch again. There was this little folder called rt0xxxx or something. &amp;lsquo;Huh&amp;rsquo;, I thought&amp;hellip; looks like some kind of realtek driver. Well, it was. A little voice tried to tell me that I spent a hella time scouring blogs trying to get my ethernet port to work and this was the fix.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Gear</title>
      <link>http://ftard.me/posts/content/gear/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2021 23:54:57 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ftard.me/posts/content/gear/</guid>
      <description>This is my &amp;rsquo;exhaustive&amp;rsquo; gear list. I will hopefully update this page regularly to include every major and minor little obscure piece of gear I own. Often times people ask me about a thing I use but I can&amp;rsquo;t remember for the life of me the name of it let alone a link to it. Like for instance my fethed or the exact mic stand I use. Please peruse and enjoy!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Git Push to Remote Server</title>
      <link>http://ftard.me/posts/git-push-to-remote-server/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 18:09:16 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ftard.me/posts/git-push-to-remote-server/</guid>
      <description>Is there a better way to get those pages out into the wild and free them from your keystrokes and up onto your web server? Yes, and even better than ftp, scp, rsync or simply drag and dropping files, at your disposal there is GIT!
Git is a free and open source distributed version control system designed to handle everything from small to very large projects with speed and efficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ssh Keys With Namecheap</title>
      <link>http://ftard.me/posts/ssh-keys-with-namecheap/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 16:47:53 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ftard.me/posts/ssh-keys-with-namecheap/</guid>
      <description>I like linux but I&amp;rsquo;m on WinDoz a lot and I use Powershell never PuTTY. I have a namecheap shared hosting plan and I can never remember how to access my site with ssh-keys, for shell access to my server and also using git for revision control and pushing content to my server. Here is a walk though using powershell.
1st check OpenSSH status on Windows. from docs.microsoft
Get-WindowsCapability -Online | ?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://ftard.me/about/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2020 16:53:07 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ftard.me/about/about/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to ftard.me! You have finaly found a site that is about you!
Or perhaps me, or you,&amp;hellip; or me you and everybody to. You may be asking &amp;lsquo;how would there be a website that knows about you the way that most everyone that knows you do?&amp;rsquo; Well the answer to that question is quite long and full of extremely boring matharymical arithmaticy AlGore-isms. I find the best way to understand is just not to at all!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My IRL Set Up</title>
      <link>http://ftard.me/posts/content/irl/irl-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2020 15:26:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ftard.me/posts/content/irl/irl-setup/</guid>
      <description>by dawjanox
!! Amazon Affiliate Links !!
Main Gear Encoder: UrayCoder Cam: GoPro Hero5 Power: Halo Bolt Mic: Rode Video Micro Mounting Gear: Mount: Woods 6 inch vacuum cup mount Arm: SMALLRIG articulating arm Ball Head: Neewer Ball Head Server/Software: NOALBS: check it on github SLS: check it on gitlab OBS-STUDIO: check the OBS Project website Linode: Here is a referral link Notes: I plan on doing a full write up of this set up but this is my gear list for IRL right now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>H265 Over Srt Headaches</title>
      <link>http://ftard.me/posts/content/irl/h265-over-srt-headaches/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2020 16:31:22 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ftard.me/posts/content/irl/h265-over-srt-headaches/</guid>
      <description>So, you have an encoder that is capable of h.264 over SRT? You want to feed the video into OBS? Have you also found that h.265 over SRT is not as well documented as say h.264 over RTMP? I bet you have and so did I. I also banged my head against walls, keyboards, tables, innocent by-standards on the street,.. in all - I - was the biggest obstacle in the way of successfully achieving my 1st SRT transmission.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
